hey everybody welcome to this A1 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as I speak before we
start remember to download the listening
Time Podcast and if you want my
specialized training to help you improve
your listening then become a member at
and understand native speakers and if
you become a listening Time family
member then you'll receive my Advanced
podcast episodes which will help you
reach an advanced level of listening
okay today we're going to talk about
breakfast this is my favorite meal of
the day so I'm happy to talk about it
first let's talk about breakfast in the
US many people think that Americans eat
a big breakfast every day you've
probably seen this in American movies
and TV shows you might see people eating
eggs bacon sausage pancakes and more
however most Americans don't eat a
really big breakfast on weekdays many
people don't have time to cook a big
breakfast before they go to work
actually it's really common for people
to just eat cereal I did this a lot when
I was a kid did but on weekends people
have more time to enjoy their breakfast
in the morning so people might eat the
type of breakfast that you see in the
movies I remember when I was a kid my
mom cooked more creative breakfasts on
Saturdays and Sundays my favorite
breakfast that my mom cooked was Crepes
I still remember how amazing they tasted
it's also common for Americans to go out
for breakfast on weekends breakfast
restaurants are really crowded on
Saturday and Sunday mornings and we also
love enjoying a nice breakfast when
we're on vacation basically when we have
the time we love to eat a good breakfast
in many other countries people don't eat
a lot for breakfast I remember when I
was in Europe I saw many people having
only a little sweet bread and coffee for
breakfast this definitely isn't enough
for me but for other people this is
enough I think that in many countries
breakfast isn't an important meal lunch
and dinner are usually more important in
the US some people say that breakfast is
the most important meal of the day what
do you think what's the most important
meal of the day for you now let me
describe my typical breakfast normally
on weekdays I eat eggs bacon and fruit I
love the combination of bacon and eggs
they go together perfectly I don't get
tired of this food even if I eat it
every day of course I always buy fresh
and organic eggs bacon and fruit this is
really important for me and on weekends
I often go to restaurants to eat
breakfast I love going out to to eat
breakfast there are a lot of amazing
breakfast restaurants where I live so I
have many options I usually eat
different breakfast foods at restaurants
one of my favorite breakfasts is a
Mexican dish called chilak kiles I order
this food all the time and I also really
like sweet breakfast foods like French
toast pancakes and sweet bread as you
can see I love breakfast
in general one other thing that I
sometimes have for breakfast is coffee I
don't drink coffee every day and I don't
really like caffeine but I really like
warm drinks so I often order coffee or
hot chocolate when I eat breakfast at
restaurants I know some people that need
coffee in the morning if they don't have
coffee then they can't start their day
I'm not like this I sometimes have
coffee with my breakfast but it's not
necessary leave a comment down below and
tell me what you eat for breakfast
remember to download my free listening
Time Podcast and become a member at
patreon.com/crashcourse listen ining
Time family member so you can train your
listening with my Advanced podcast
episodes also subscribe to the channel
click on the bell and follow us on
Instagram I'll see you next time
[Music]